ents24.com 2012-05-23

# Privacy Policy - Ents24

This privacy policy sets out how Ents24 Ltd ('Ents24') uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website. 

Ents24 is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

Ents24 may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 8 January 2010. 

### Information Collection and Use

Ents24 collects information about you when your register on the website, when you purchase tickets, and when you visit the Ents24 web pages. Ents24 may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. 

**Registration.** During the registration process, a user is required to give their full name and email address. It is optional for the user to provide further information about their interests and demographic information (such as gender and date of birth), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalised experience. 

**Ticket Purchase.** When purchasing tickets, customers are required to give their full name, postal address, email address and daytime telephone number so that we can fulfill the order and get in touch if there is a problem. 

**Correspondence.** If you contact Ents24 by email, post or fax, we may keep a record of that correspondence. 

**Other Information.** Ents24 automatically receives and records information from your browser including your IP address and the page you requested. 

**Cookies.** Read further information here about Ents24's use of cookies.

### Sharing of Information

When you purchase tickets, Ents24 may pass your personally identifiable information to other companies so that they can post the tickets you have requested and/or charge your card for the order. They may also contact you on our behalf if there is a problem with your order. Unless we tell you beforehand, they do not have the right to use your information for any other purpose. 

We may also send information about you to other companies to provide services or products you have specifically requested, such as competition prizes. 

Other than in the cases above, Ents24 will not release your personally identifiable information to other parties, unless you explicitly give your consent during the registration process or at a later date. 

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify individuals. 

### Editing your Account Information

If you would like to alter your account information or preferences at any time, please log into the website using the username and password you chose during registration. 

### Deleting your Personal Details

If you would like us to completely delete your personal details from our server, please . 

### Accessing your information

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Ents24 Ltd., Technology House, 16-18 Whiteladies Road, BRISTOL BS8 2LG. 

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to us as soon as possible, at the above address, or email us. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

### Enquiries

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please .
